Guide to the Yale Residential Colleges Student Printing Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- Residential College Books and Ephemera, Series III
  - Books
    - Trumbull College
      - Bethune, Elizabeth R. de, 1979 (Box 4)
      - Billett, Amy L., 1979; 2 bound copies; 1 unbound copy (Box 4)
      - McCreary, James, 1979 (Box 4)
      - Means, Kimberly, 1986 (Box 4)
      - Trumbull College. Gargoyle, 1981 (Box 4)
      - Vernooy, Paul, 1986 (Box 4)
    - Yale College
      These materials have no specified residential college.
      - Ancient Customs, undated (Box 15)
      - The Book of Leonard, undated (Box 15)
      - Cochran, Kevin, 1984 (Box 4)
      - Comic Review, 2002 (Box 4)
      - Harley, Galen, 1965; 2 (Box 4)
      - Johnson, Carrie, 1980 (Box 4)
      - Johnson, Carrie, 1981 (Box 12)
      - The Jolly Tinker, undated (Box 15)
      - Lichten, Dave, 1972 (Box 4)
      - Lobe Den Herren, undated (Box 15)
      - Marson, Edward, undated (Box 4)
      - Polikoff, Joan, 1981 (Box 4)
      - Roberts, Leslie, 1978 (Box 4)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, volume XI, number 2, 2000 (Box 4)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, volume XII, number 1, 2000 (Box 4)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, volume XIV, number 1, 2002 (Box 4)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, volume 14, number 2 (and ephemera), 2002-2003 (Box 20)
      - Yale Literary Magazine, volume 18, number 1 Spring 2007, 2006-2007 (Box 4)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 11)
      - Unidentified, undated (Box 20)
  - Ephemera
    - Berkeley College
      - Ephemera, 1974-1992 (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 5)
    - Branford College
      - Ephemera, 1937-1941 undated (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, 1938-1980 (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, 1981-1984 (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, 1988-1990 (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, 1998-2006 (Box 5)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 5)
    - Calhoun College
      - Ephemera, 1979-1982 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 1982-1984 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, undated; 2 (Box 6)
    - Davenport College
      - Ephemera, 1968-1972 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 1976-1988 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 1998-2003 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 2005-2006 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, undated; 4 (Box 6)
      - Ephemera, 1988-1992 undated (Box 14)
    - Ezra Stiles College
      - Ephemera, 1978-1992 undated (Box 6)
    - Jonathan Edwards College
      - Ephemera, 1934-1966 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1967-1968 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1969-1970 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1971-1972 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1973 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1974 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1975-1976 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1977-1979 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1980-1981 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1982-1984 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1985-1987 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1988; 2 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1989; 2 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1992-1994 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 1999-2004 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, 2005-2006 (Box 7)
      - Ephemera, undated; 4 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1970-2004 undated (Box 14)
    - Morse College
      - Ephemera, 1983-1991 (Box 8)
    - Pierson College
      - Ephemera, 1966-1972 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1977 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1978 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1979; 2 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1980 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1981 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1982 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1983 (Box 8)
        For years 1984-1986, see Box 9.
      - Ephemera, 1988 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1989; 2 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1990 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1991 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1992 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 2003-2006 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, undated; 5 (Box 8)
      - Ephemera, 1984-1986 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1972-2003 undated (Box 14)
    - Saybrook College
      - Ephemera, 1979-1988 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1989-2002 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1984-1990 undated (Box 14)
    - Silliman College
      - Ephemera, 1972-1979 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1981-1989 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1990-2006 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1984-1990 undated (Box 14)
    - Timothy Dwight College
      - Ephemera, 1936-1956 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1962-1979 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1980-1990 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, undated (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1988-1992 undated (Box 14)
    - Trumbull College
      - Ephemera, 1978-1979 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1979 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1980; 4 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1981; 4 (Box 9)
      - Ephemera, 1982; 8 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1983; 7 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1984; 6 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1985; 2 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1986; 4 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1987 (Box 10)
      - Ephemera, 1988-2005 (Box 11)
      - Ephemera, undated; 10 (Box 11)
      - Ephemera, 1978-1995 undated (Box 14)
    - Yale College
      - Ephemera, 1940-1992 undated; 19 (Box 15)
      - Ephemera, 1973-1979 undated (Box 14)
      - Ephemera (Folder 1)